Rafaella Sena Toronto, ON M4S 0B13800

Summary

I am environmental engineering with over five years of experience. For the last four years in São Paulo, I have been working in environmental projects and startups, I supervised companies' licenses and certification processes, and also created a sales channel from scratch, which in only 5 months has guaranteed over 300 tons of packaging material to be recycled or compensated in Brazil.

I will be dedicated for the next 1 year to the post-graduation course on Project Management which provides me only part-time availability to work, period that I want to focus on fulfilling part of my learning curve by working closely to project leaders and adjusting my previous experiences to the Canadian market.

Skills

- Reducing environmental impact
- Scheduling and calendar management
- Team Leadership
- Business Development
- Sales

- Project support
- Goals and Performance
- Strong enthusiasm
- Communication skills
- Problem solving strength
- Strategy
- Market Research

· Microsoft Office

Cel: 647-382-3800

e-mail: rafaella sena@hotmail.com

- Excel, Word
- Portuguese
- English
- Analytical
- Research
- Planning

Experience

LCIT PM Guild – Lambton College

October 2020 - current

Administration Manager Volunteer

Prepare and disseminate meeting minutes, assist with the organizing of internal guild events, liaise with marketing team to follow up the flyers

Toronto Environmental Alliance

September 2020 - current

Volunteer

Volunteer at Zero Waste High-Rise Project, online program that allows residents to start the process of reducing. I am co-responsible to achieve sustainable standards.

Downtown Winery Customer Service

July 2020 - current

NewHope Ecotech

2018-2020

3. New Business Coordinator

May 2020 to September 2020

- Structuring a new sales channel
- Deliver sales training programs
- Manage teams of + 15 sales representative
- Interview, training and developing people

2. Senior Sales

January 2020 to May 2020

- Attending conferences, meetings, and industry events
- Researched and recommended new processes in solid waste to reduce environmental damages, reducing damages at least 22%
- Contact internal and external stakeholders to get more information when required

1. Junior Sales

August 2018 to January 2020

- Environmental Certification
- Outbound Prospecting
- Customer relationship management
- Preparation of proposals

Sotreq 2017-2018

Commercial Analyst

• Participated in requirements meetings and data mapping sessions to understand business needs

FEAM 2015-2017

Scientific Researcher

- Internet-research to clarify information such as legal entity, their business activity and scope of operations.
- Input information of companies into government database
- Propose solutions to reduce environmental impact

Education

Lambton College

Expected in 2022

Master of Business Administration - MBA Project Management and Strategic Leadership

CEFET - MG Belo Horizonte, Brazil

June 2010 to June 2016

Bachelor's degree Environmental Engineering Technology/Environmental Technology

University Of New South Wales Sydney, Australia

October 2013 to December 2014

Sandwich Course Environmental Engineering Technology/Environmental Technology